



619-0224, 1-chōme-2 Kabutodai, Kizugawa-shi, Kyōto-fu, Japan

□ (+81) 90-2287-8846 | ■ dcy0921@outlook.com | ★ dangchenyu.github.io | • dangchenyu

"Everything has its time and that time must be watched."

Summary.

Current Master student in Nara Institute Of Science And Technology(NAIST), expected to graduate in Sept.2020. Research interest include computer vision(Object detection/Multi-Object Tracking) and ubiquitous computing. Got Bachelor's degree in vehicle engineering in Chang'an University. Have almost two years work experience in China Chang'an Automobile Group. Willing to face new challenges and looking forward to transforming the advanced AI technologies into creative products.

Education

Chang'an University Xi'an, China

Sep. 2011 - Jul. 2015 B.S. IN VEHICLE ENGINEERING

- Final year ranking: 19/174
- Got Scholarship in second and third year
- Vice-president of the Student's Science and Technology Association

JCL Japanese language school

JAPANESE LEARNING

• Got all A at final evaluation

Nara Institute Of Science And Technology

M.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

- Ubiquitous Computing Systems Lab
- · Hired as research assistant
- · Leader of student creative project contest

Work Experience _____

Changan Automobile Co., Ltd.

ChongQing, China

Kyoto, Janpan Apr. 2017 - Feb. 2018

Nara, Janpan

Oct. 2018 - Exp. Stp. 2020

AIR INTAKE DESIGN ENGINEER

Aug. 2015 - Mar. 2017

- Responsible for development of air intake system and it's layout in engine room \(\)Cooperate with other departments to push forward the project (CS55, Yuexiang v7)
- Responsible for the entire process from supplier bidding to product acceptance
- Familiar with vehicle and it's component development process
- Serve as youth corps secretary in department, organize activities for youth employee

Skills

Programming Python, C, LaTeX **Deep learning** Pytorch, Tensorflow Languages Chinese, English, Japanese

Honors & Awards

2013 **Third Scholarship**, Chang'an University(Shaanxi Fast Gear Group)

2013 Advanced Individuals, Summer Social Practice

2014 **Excellent Student Leader**, Chang'an University

2014 **Second Scholarship**, Chang'an University(Shaanxi Fast Gear Group)

2017 Excellent new employee, Powertrain Appendix Dept., Changan Automobile

Hobby_

Playing basketball | Mountain climbing | Singing

CHENYU DANG · RÉSUMÉ